var content = [
  {
    question: 'Which term describes a plan of action designed to achieve a specific goal?',
    answers: {
      right: 'strategy',
      wrong: ['business model', 'marketing', 'leadership message']
    },
    explain: 'The answer is strategy. A good strategy defines a clear vision for your desired outcome, and identifies the steps needed to acheive that outcome.'
  },
  {
    question: 'Select the word that descibes the systematic and comprehensive recording of financial transactions pertaining to a business.',
    answers: {
      right: 'accounting',
      wrong: ['economics', 'notetaking', 'investing']
    },
    explain: 'The answer is accounting. Accounting also includes the process of summarizing, analyzing, and reporting your transactions to oversight agencies and the IRS for tax collection.'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which of the following are NOT one of the 4 P\'s of marketing?',
    answers: {
      right: 'personality',
      wrong: ['price', 'product', 'place']
    },
    explain: 'The 4 P\'s of marketing include: product, price, place, and promotional strategy.'
  },
  {
    question: '____ is the capacity to influence others to acheive common goals.',
    answers: {
      right: 'leadership',
      wrong: ['management', 'scheduling', 'public speaking']
    },
    explain: 'This one was a little tricky. Leadership is the capacity to influence others, while management is assigned leadership to produce order and consistency.'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which of these is a part of the risk management process?',
    answers: {
      right: 'identification',
      wrong: ['panicking', 'assigning blame', 'procrastinating']
    },
    explain: 'Risk management is a process to identify, assess, and mitigate or avoid risks.'
  },
  {
    question: 'What is it called when one firm, usually larger, purchases some or all of another firm\'s assets?',
    answers: {
      right: 'acquisition',
      wrong: ['merger', 'bankruptcy', 'invasion']
    },
    explain: 'When one company purchases another, this is an acqusition. This is not always a bad thing - some are friendly, while others are perceived as hostile takeovers.'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which of these is an example of offline media?',
    answers: {
      right: 'television',
      wrong: ['website', 'email', 'mobile app']
    },
    explain: 'TV, radio, print magazines, newspapers, billboards, etc. are all considered offline media.'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which of these is the correct order of a buyer\'s journey?',
    answers: {
      right: 'awareness > interest > consideration > evaluation > purchase',
      wrong: ['consideration > awareness > interest > purchase > evaluation', 'interest > purchase >consideration > awareness > evaluation', 'evaluation > consideration > awareness > interest > purchase']
    },
    explain: 'Marketers should tailor activities to each stage of the buyer\'s journey, i.e. the process consumers go through before they buy: <br/><br/> awareness > interest > consideration > evaluation > purchase'
  },
  {
    question: 'An effective mission statement answers 4 key questions about a company. Which of the following is NOT one of these key questions?',
    answers: {
      right: 'How much does our product cost?',
      wrong: ['What do we provide?', 'Who are our customers?', 'What is important to us?']
    },
    explain: 'A mission statement is an explanation of why a company exists, and how it aims to serve its stakeholders. It should answer:<br/><br/> a) What do we provide?<br/> b) Who are our customers?<br/> c) What is the benefit?<br/> d) What is important to us?<br/><br/> Tesla\'s mission statement, for example, is: To accelerate the advent of sustainable transport by bringing compelling mass market electric cars to market as soon as possible.'
  },
  {
    question: 'What does a vision statement describe?',
    answers: {
      right: 'a big picture of where the company wants to go',
      wrong: ['the ideal outcomes for customers', 'the steps needed to achieve company goals', 'company values and ethics']
    },
    explain: 'The vision statement should be future-oriented and define what the company aims to become. For example, Google\'s vision statement is: â€œTo provide access to the worlds information in one click.""'
  }
]
